question_data = [
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Igneous rocks are formed by excessive heat and pressure.",
    "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "The &quot;Gympie Stinger&quot; is the deadliest plant in the world.",
    "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Like with the Neanderthals, Homo sapiens sapiens also interbred with the Denisovans.",
    "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "It was once believed that injecting shark cartilage into people would prevent them from contracting cancer.",
    "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Anatomy considers the forms of macroscopic structures such as organs and organ systems.",
    "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Salt is 100% composed of Sodium.", "correct_answer": "False",
    "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "An atom contains a nucleus.", "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Pneumonoultramicroscopicsilicovolcanoconiosis is a synonym for the disease known as silicosis.",
    "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Sound can travel through a vacuum.", "correct_answer": "False",
    "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "The most frequent subconscious activity repeated by the human body is blinking.",
    "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
